<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Avicii on Lindskold</title>
    <link>https://somiew.github.io/tags/avicii/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Avicii on Lindskold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.0</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://somiew.github.io/tags/avicii/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The White Avicii Nintendo Switch Lite</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/the-white-avicii-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/the-white-avicii-switch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nintendo has done a lot of custom coloured Switches, especially of the standard Switch. The &amp;rsquo;lite&amp;rsquo; version though, mostly has some basic recolours. And a couple of Pokémon variants. But there is one Switch Lite that stands out of the crew. The white, custom gold painted Avicii Invector Switch Lite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2017 &lt;a href=&#34;https://hellotheregames.com/&#34;&gt;Hello There Games&lt;/a&gt; released &amp;lsquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3oWAqf5ckvU&#34;&gt;Invector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo; on the PS4. A rhythm based music game with 22 of Aviciis hit songs. In 2019, the year after his tragic passing, they released an updated version with 35 songs, in collaboration with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.timberglingfoundation.org/&#34;&gt;Tim Bergling Foundation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nintendo.com/store/products/avicii-invector-encore-edition-switch/&#34;&gt;Avicii Invector: Encore Edition&lt;/a&gt;, and with the release, there was a charity auction, where all the money gathered went to the mental health organisation, &lt;a href=&#34;https://safeinourworld.org/&#34;&gt;Safe In Our World&lt;/a&gt;. This is where the rare Switch Lite enters the stage. Five beautiful custom painted switches were auctioned out. And what makes them extra special is that they&amp;rsquo;re actually licensed by Nintendo. Many companies has had lotteries or the like with custom painted or shells swapped switches, but this is actually a fully legit licensed Nintendo Switch Lite, and it. Is. Beautiful!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
