<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lindskold</title>
    <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lindskold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.0</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://somiew.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rullade speleftertexter 2024</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2025/rullade-speleftertexter-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2025/rullade-speleftertexter-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2022 - 8 spel&lt;br&gt;
2023 - 5 spel&lt;br&gt;
2024 - BAM! 13 spel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Men innan jag går in på spelen ett och ett, så tänker jag att vi kopplar tillbaka till förra årets slutkläm, spelen jag hoppades ta mig igenom 2024. Dessa var:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hogwarts Legacy (check)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baldur’s Gate 3 (nope)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Death Stranding (also no)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avatar Frontiers of Pandora (nu-uh)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Super Mario Wonder (yes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2/5 ändå.
Death stranding och Avatar har jag väl lagt på is, på obestämt framtid. Men Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3 började jag om på, ihop med Jasmine, och vi har ändå tagit oss en bra bit in på tredje akten nu. Så det kommer få stå kvar för 2025.
Med det sagt, låt oss gå in lite kort på spelen jag faktiskt slutförde.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>117</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2024/117/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2024/117/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I slutet av december fick jag upp lite randomly upp en challange på Youtube, prata med 100 personer inom spannet av en månad. Den var väl mer menad för folk som känner att de lever i sin egna bubbla framför en skärm, men vad vet jag, det kanske faktiskt skulle tvinga mig till att bli mer social.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regler&lt;br&gt;
Det måste finnas dialog.&lt;br&gt;
Att säga hej till random personer på stan räknas, om de svarar. Men det kanske inte är det roligaste sättet klara det på.&lt;br&gt;
Att prata via telefon räknas, men inte text.&lt;br&gt;
I gruppsamtal räknas endast de man har 1-på-1 konversationer med.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rullade speleftertexter 2023</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2024/rullade-speleftertexter-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2024/rullade-speleftertexter-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tillskillnad från 2022, då jag rullade eftertexter i hela åtta spel, blev det bara fem i år.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Diablo IV&lt;/em&gt; (2023)&lt;br&gt;
Spelade på release, fram till jag blev klar med det. Mer eller mindre. Någon kort paus på en vecka mitt i tror jag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Storyteller&lt;/em&gt; (2023)&lt;br&gt;
Fanns via Netflix, jag och Jasmine körde igenom det samtidigt, på varsin telefon, en bana i taget och tävlade om vem som kom på lösningen först. Kul och mysigt.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jag sprang!</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/jag-sprang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/jag-sprang/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;För 3 veckor sedan fick jag en &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;fix idé&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;, en &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;dille&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo; så att säga, en riktig &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;käpphäst&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;. Ni vet, en &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;mono-mani&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;. Vi var ute på stan när jag fick syn på en banderoll som gjorde reklam för &lt;a href=&#34;https://malmoloppet.se/&#34;&gt;Malmöloppet&lt;/a&gt;. Jag berättade för min partner att jag var lite sugen på att skriva upp mig, för att&amp;hellip; Varför inte? Jag har aldrig sprungit något stadslopp förr. Motfrågan jag fick var:&lt;br&gt;
- Hur långt får det max vara för att du ska LOVA att göra det?&lt;br&gt;
Dum som jag är tänkte jag att loppet självklart är 10 km, jag kan väl helt enkelt säga hälften? 5 km.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Tomato &amp; G-Shock</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/blue-tomato-g-shock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/blue-tomato-g-shock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I vintras fastnade jag för en ny klädbutik. Blue Tomato. Jag gillar typ hela deras utbud. Kanske inte ALLT, och jag tror ju absolut inte att jag PASSAR i allt. Men mycket av det kan jag ändå uppskatta. En av dessa saker, som har etsat sig fast i min hjärna, är en klocka.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blue-tomato.com/sv-SE/product/G+SHOCK-DW+5610DN+9ER+Klocka-632414/?varid=304384693&#34;&gt;G-SHOCK DW-5610DN-9ER&lt;/a&gt;, eller som butikspersonalen refererar till den, legoklockan. En klassisk digital G-Shock med en stor skillnad. Färgen. Istället för svart är den: röd, gul, grön, orange, lila och ljusblå. Med en digital display av svart på vitt. Man kan lätt förstå var namnet &amp;rsquo;legoklockan&amp;rsquo; har sitt ursprung, då det ser ut som om någon har byggt ihop den av färgglada bitar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Pokémon Snap</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/old-pokemon-snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/old-pokemon-snap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A week or two ago I started playing a game I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about playing ever since the sequel was announced, over 20 years after the first game. Pokémon Snap. Admittedly I first thought about buying the new game, &amp;lsquo;New Pokémon Snap&amp;rsquo;. But it felt a bit expensive for a rail shooter in 2021, especially since its coming from a game company that doesn&amp;rsquo;t really care. So I thought I&amp;rsquo;d wait for a while, see if the price dropped. Not very long after however, Nintendo announced that the original Pokémon Snap would come to Nintendo Online. So my plan changed, and I was to try the original first, and if I liked it, I would consider buying the new one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Hawk&#39;s™ Pro Skater™ 1 &#43; 2</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/thps1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/thps1-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A while ago I beat THPS 1+2 for the fifth time and it&amp;rsquo;s still as good of a game as the first time. I never played the originals when they released, but I did play a lot of Tony Hawk as a kid. THPS 3 was the first in the series I played, a cousin lent it to me after I had gotten hold of a used PlayStation 2. It was a great game, but I had heard that there were better Tony Hawk games. Underground 1 and 2, where it was possible to throw tomatoes, ride a bull and spray your own tag across the city. But most importantly, you didn&amp;rsquo;t need to ride ALL the time. If you wanted to aim for a specific jump or go for a certain rail, it was possible to get off the board and walk there. Eventually I got to play these games as well, at friends places and sometimes I even got to borrow them for short periods of time, but my first ever own Tony Hawk&amp;rsquo;s, was American Wasteland.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White Avicii Nintendo Switch Lite</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/the-white-avicii-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/the-white-avicii-switch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nintendo has done a lot of custom coloured Switches, especially of the standard Switch. The &amp;rsquo;lite&amp;rsquo; version though, mostly has some basic recolours. And a couple of Pokémon variants. But there is one Switch Lite that stands out of the crew. The white, custom gold painted Avicii Invector Switch Lite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2017 &lt;a href=&#34;https://hellotheregames.com/&#34;&gt;Hello There Games&lt;/a&gt; released &amp;lsquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3oWAqf5ckvU&#34;&gt;Invector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo; on the PS4. A rhythm based music game with 22 of Aviciis hit songs. In 2019, the year after his tragic passing, they released an updated version with 35 songs, in collaboration with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.timberglingfoundation.org/&#34;&gt;Tim Bergling Foundation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nintendo.com/store/products/avicii-invector-encore-edition-switch/&#34;&gt;Avicii Invector: Encore Edition&lt;/a&gt;, and with the release, there was a charity auction, where all the money gathered went to the mental health organisation, &lt;a href=&#34;https://safeinourworld.org/&#34;&gt;Safe In Our World&lt;/a&gt;. This is where the rare Switch Lite enters the stage. Five beautiful custom painted switches were auctioned out. And what makes them extra special is that they&amp;rsquo;re actually licensed by Nintendo. Many companies has had lotteries or the like with custom painted or shells swapped switches, but this is actually a fully legit licensed Nintendo Switch Lite, and it. Is. Beautiful!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 1 of 1 Ring</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/the1of1ring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/the1of1ring/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple days ago Wizards of the Coast revealed some cards for the new Lord of the Rings crossover set. One of which was &amp;ldquo;The One Ring&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;The One Ring&amp;rdquo;, is going to have a special &lt;em&gt;special&lt;/em&gt; edition - extended art with text in elvish (Quenya in Tengwar letterform to be exact, if that tells you anything you&amp;rsquo;re a huge NERD). This card, among some others, will be what they call serialized. Numbered card, that show exactly which card you got, from a limited print run.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co - Star</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/co-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/co-star/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I learned about Co-Star, and therefore, so will you!&lt;br&gt;
It&amp;rsquo;s an astrology app, and just like many others like it, it gives the user a daily horoscope. But this one is special, because this one is &amp;ldquo;based on science&amp;rdquo;. It uses data from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/&#34;&gt;NASA JPL&lt;/a&gt; and the &amp;ldquo;magic of dates and AI&amp;rdquo;, to find patterns and create horoscopes. Created by Banu Guler, a woman who, ackording to Wikipedia, once brought an astrological chart to a baby shower, where she noticed it was such a hit, she decided to create an app for it. 🤷. Wild stuff. She does however have a killer &lt;a href=&#34;https://banuguler.com/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;, so go check that one out!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAR10</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/mar10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 17:42:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/mar10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;March 10, a.k.a. MAR10 day. First celebrated by Nintendo 2016,
probably when some clever Nintendian came up with the idea.
And since then, they’ve actually made something each year to celebrate Mario,
even if some years have been lazier than others.
This year we got the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DdD9geN6erk&#34;&gt;final trailer&lt;/a&gt; for
The Super Mario Bros. Movie, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nintendo.com/whatsnew/wave-4-is-out-now-for-the-mario-kart-8-deluxe-booster-course-pass-dlc/&#34;&gt;Wave 4&lt;/a&gt; of the Mario Kart 8 Deluxe –
Booster Course Pass (car stuff, pretty fitting since it’s also the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.scania.com/group/en/home/newsroom/news/2020/international-v8-day-old-meets-new.html&#34;&gt;V8 engines day&lt;/a&gt; today) and a new
Mario themed &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nintendo.com/store/products/nintendo-switch-mario-choose-one-bundle-118107/&#34;&gt;Nintendo Switch bundle&lt;/a&gt;. And lots of smaller stuff as well.
Like whatever &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h4nq-JDPDgA&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; is.
I must admit though, I am pretty hyped for the movie, so another trailer is always welcome!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games man</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/games_man/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 17:42:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/games_man/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been playing a lot of games lately. Or… A lot of games for the very limited amount of spare time I have at hands. It’s been loads for fun though. More fun than I have had gaming in a long long time.
I quite recently bought a new graphics card, and I guess I have to attribute my newfound joy to this, as I’ve not been able to enjoy AAA titles to their extent in recent years.
Don’t get me wrong, many smaller game studios make incredible games as well, but it’s something special to get a full experience of a game that was made of hundreds of people over several years. At least if it’s done well. And let me tell you about a game that does it REALLY well! &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Forza_Horizon_5&#34;&gt;Forza Horizon 5&lt;/a&gt; Holy hell is it a well made game. Big open world. Lots of stuff to unlock. Many corners to dig deep into.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hell!-oh and welcome to my website!</title>
      <link>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/hell-oh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 17:42:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://somiew.github.io/posts/2023/hell-oh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my very own little nook on the internet, where I try out new things, show off what I like and generally just do whatever I want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now it’s a bit under construction, and in a way I think it always will be. Hopyfully this page will always keep growing with new side projects popping up here and there.🤞
&amp;#x1f648;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
