<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nintendo on Lindskold</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/nintendo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nintendo on Lindskold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.0</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/nintendo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gameboy Advance SP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025/gameboy-advance-sp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025/gameboy-advance-sp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whaaats&amp;rsquo;up?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;För några veckor sedan gjorde jag ett impulsköp av ett Gameboy Advance SP,
då en polare lyckades få tag i 3 gameboys till ett hyffsat bra pris.
Han var inte superhype på just SP&amp;rsquo;et, vilket råkade vara precis den jag var mest intresserad av.
Tanken för oss båda var att köpa in lite grejer, och uppa dem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Från början hade jag väl planerat att köpa ett nytt skal + en IPS skärm,
men efter lite research insåg jag att
&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/vWikZ-u8pCI?si=2Z--R1zWzyI4gqX-&amp;amp;t=380&#34;&gt;batteritiden&lt;/a&gt;
kommer ta sig en törn av det.
Dessutom måste man då köra på full ljusstyrka om man vill använda den i solen.
Medan originalskärmen kan stänga av belysningen helt, för att man ska kunna använda den i direkt solljus
(vilket händer oftare än man skulle kunna ana på tåget till Köpenhamn).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Pokémon Snap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/old-pokemon-snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/old-pokemon-snap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A week or two ago I started playing a game I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about playing ever since the sequel was announced, over 20 years after the first game. Pokémon Snap. Admittedly I first thought about buying the new game, &amp;lsquo;New Pokémon Snap&amp;rsquo;. But it felt a bit expensive for a rail shooter in 2021, especially since its coming from a game company that doesn&amp;rsquo;t really care. So I thought I&amp;rsquo;d wait for a while, see if the price dropped. Not very long after however, Nintendo announced that the original Pokémon Snap would come to Nintendo Online. So my plan changed, and I was to try the original first, and if I liked it, I would consider buying the new one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Hawk&#39;s™ Pro Skater™ 1 &#43; 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/thps1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/thps1-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A while ago I beat THPS 1+2 for the fifth time and it&amp;rsquo;s still as good of a game as the first time. I never played the originals when they released, but I did play a lot of Tony Hawk as a kid. THPS 3 was the first in the series I played, a cousin lent it to me after I had gotten hold of a used PlayStation 2. It was a great game, but I had heard that there were better Tony Hawk games. Underground 1 and 2, where it was possible to throw tomatoes, ride a bull and spray your own tag across the city. But most importantly, you didn&amp;rsquo;t need to ride ALL the time. If you wanted to aim for a specific jump or go for a certain rail, it was possible to get off the board and walk there. Eventually I got to play these games as well, at friends places and sometimes I even got to borrow them for short periods of time, but my first ever own Tony Hawk&amp;rsquo;s, was American Wasteland.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White Avicii Nintendo Switch Lite</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/the-white-avicii-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/the-white-avicii-switch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nintendo has done a lot of custom coloured Switches, especially of the standard Switch. The &amp;rsquo;lite&amp;rsquo; version though, mostly has some basic recolours. And a couple of Pokémon variants. But there is one Switch Lite that stands out of the crew. The white, custom gold painted Avicii Invector Switch Lite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2017 &lt;a href=&#34;https://hellotheregames.com/&#34;&gt;Hello There Games&lt;/a&gt; released &amp;lsquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3oWAqf5ckvU&#34;&gt;Invector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo; on the PS4. A rhythm based music game with 22 of Aviciis hit songs. In 2019, the year after his tragic passing, they released an updated version with 35 songs, in collaboration with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.timberglingfoundation.org/&#34;&gt;Tim Bergling Foundation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nintendo.com/store/products/avicii-invector-encore-edition-switch/&#34;&gt;Avicii Invector: Encore Edition&lt;/a&gt;, and with the release, there was a charity auction, where all the money gathered went to the mental health organisation, &lt;a href=&#34;https://safeinourworld.org/&#34;&gt;Safe In Our World&lt;/a&gt;. This is where the rare Switch Lite enters the stage. Five beautiful custom painted switches were auctioned out. And what makes them extra special is that they&amp;rsquo;re actually licensed by Nintendo. Many companies has had lotteries or the like with custom painted or shells swapped switches, but this is actually a fully legit licensed Nintendo Switch Lite, and it. Is. Beautiful!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAR10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/mar10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 17:42:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/mar10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;March 10, a.k.a. MAR10 day. First celebrated by Nintendo 2016,
probably when some clever Nintendian came up with the idea.
And since then, they’ve actually made something each year to celebrate Mario,
even if some years have been lazier than others.
This year we got the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DdD9geN6erk&#34;&gt;final trailer&lt;/a&gt; for
The Super Mario Bros. Movie, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nintendo.com/whatsnew/wave-4-is-out-now-for-the-mario-kart-8-deluxe-booster-course-pass-dlc/&#34;&gt;Wave 4&lt;/a&gt; of the Mario Kart 8 Deluxe –
Booster Course Pass (car stuff, pretty fitting since it’s also the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.scania.com/group/en/home/newsroom/news/2020/international-v8-day-old-meets-new.html&#34;&gt;V8 engines day&lt;/a&gt; today) and a new
Mario themed &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nintendo.com/store/products/nintendo-switch-mario-choose-one-bundle-118107/&#34;&gt;Nintendo Switch bundle&lt;/a&gt;. And lots of smaller stuff as well.
Like whatever &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h4nq-JDPDgA&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; is.
I must admit though, I am pretty hyped for the movie, so another trailer is always welcome!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
